Adelaide, Australia

□ (+61) 410 256 252 | Soleksii.mostovyi@gmail.com | 🛠 www.oleksiimostovyi.com | 🖸 olimstv | 🛅 olimstv

"Experience is the only thing we can truly own in our lives..."

Summary.

A software developer with a background in automation testing.

I genuinely believe that our World can become much better if every living being had the most positive life experience. I see tremendous opportunities to contribute to the improvement of people's life experiences by developing software solutions. Therefore I would love to join a team of like-minded people, where I can effectively grow and apply my professional and personal skills to benefit the community.

Skills_

Front-end HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Next.js, Gatsby.js

Back-end Node.js, Express, REST API, Ruby, Rails

Databases MongoDB, SQL, PostgreSQL DevOps Heroku, AWS, Docker, Jenkins **Languages** English, Ukrainian, Russian

Work Experience _____

Web Design Café Adelaide, Australia

PM/QA

Sep. 2021 - present • Developing web pages for the clients

- · Customising CSS of WordPress themes
- Setting up WordPress plugins · Communication with the clients
- · Organisation and coordination of the team

General Assembly Australia

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Nov. 2020 - Aug. 2021

During the course I have built a number of projects using different technologies stacks. The most mature of them is Resume Builder App - The open-source web application for fast and easy creation and publishing (with unique public URL) of resumes 'tailored' for each particular vacancy.

- lets.Get(IT) built using React, Next.js, MongoDB. Building this application, I've learned that integration of different technologies into one app might be challenging, but also it gives a significant improvement of developer's skills and knowledge base
- Memo a simple notes-gathering app, built with React and Ruby on Rails, using PostgreSQL database. Learning how to build a backend using Ruby on Rails has broadened my perspective as a developer
- CountLess a budget app that helps track incomes and spending. Main focus for this project was building backend. I learned how to protect routes, how to use Passport.js package and a basics of SSR using Handlebars

Relocation Australia

Feb. 2019 - Nov. 2020

During this period (after moving to Australia), I put all my efforts into settling on the new place, learned a new culture, and embraced a commitment towards change and personal development. I continued my self-education in Software Development until I decided to take a leap and enrolled in a Full Stack Software Engineering Immersive course of General Assembly

GlobalLogic Lviv, Ukraine

SOFTWARE AUTOMATION TEST ENGINEER

Nov. 2017 - Feb. 2019 and Sep. 2015 -

Jun. 2017

- · Testing software for a medical device (insulin pump), utilizing a custom set of frameworks and libraries, using JavaScript language.
- Writing test scripts and test scenarios to meet acceptance criteria and quality standards
- Performing formal testing to provide the results for the Federal Drug Administration (FDA)
- Automated test code-review and test stabilization
- Reviewing design inputs according to the scope of testing issues
- Creation and updating of UI and Functional Test Cases (manual and automation)
- System components and functions analysis
- · Performing iteration analysis and test planning
- · Participation in knowledge-sharing activities

Rolique Lviv, Ukraine

QUALITY ASSURANCE TEST ENGINEER

Jul. 2017 - Nov. 2017

- Testing of a CRM web application for the "INTERMATE Media GmbH".
- · Manual testing of the developing features and regression testing, writing product, and test documentation
- Analyzing client requests for validity and feasibility
- Documenting results of test execution and bug reporting
- Performing fortnightly demos for presentation to the product owners

QALight Kyiv, Ukraine

SOFTWARE TESTING AUTOMATION ENGINEER

jun. 2014 - Sep. 2015

Sep. 2003 - Jun. 1007

Testing a Social Event Discovery Platform – a web-based platform that delivers content and information on entertainment and business events within Europe.

Primary responsibilities: manual testing of the developing features and regression testing.

- · Analyzed business requirements and suggested improvements to the product features
- Developed test cases for functional and regression testing of the project Actify
- Validated application's GUI for compliance with Usability guidelines published by US Department of Human Services

Education

General Assembly

Australia

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING IMMERSIVE Nov. 2020 - May. 2021

Full Stack Web Development course

QA Light Training Centre

Kyiv, Ukraine

SOFTWARE TESTING AND QUALITY ASSURANCE

Dec. 2014 - Jul. 2015

- Software Testing and Quality Assurance
- Networking
- SQL

Donetsk Music College

Donetsk, Ukraine

BACHELOR OF MUSIC

- Music Art
- · Music Teacher
- Percussions
- · Brass Opchestra
- · Symphony Orchestra

Interests & Passions

Music Professional musician, Drummer, Music teacher, Sound Engineering, Video Production

Psychology Neurophysiology, Psycho-analysis, Behavioral Psychology, Cognitive Psychology

Philosophy Stoicism, Vedic Philosophy, Buddhism, Zen